Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University website collection
2009-2014
SC1015
Stanford University
479272 megabyte(s) (2,711,689 files in 1,068,700 directories)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Accruals
Sites selected for inclusion in the collection are scheduled for capture on a recurring basis, usually at least once per year.
Physical Characteristics / Technical Requirements
The websites were captured using HTTrack, a free offline browser utility. HTTrack downloads a website from the Internet to a local directory, building recursively all directories, getting HTML, images, and other files from the server to your computer. HTTrack arranges the original site's relative link-structure allowing you to open a page of the mirrored website in your browser, browse the site from link to link.
Scope and Contents note
The materials consist of Stanford University websites captured by University Archives staff. Included are the websites of Stanford's seven schools, their departments, and many school-affiliated labs and research centers; independent research centers and institutes reporting to the Dean of Research; interdisciplinary programs; and administrative units overseeing academic affairs, faculty development, student life, research, public affairs, human resources, and other areas of the university. Also included are sites providing information on campus events, such as Commencement and Parents' Weekend; sites established to disseminate information on specific initiatives, such as the Stanford in NYC proposal of 2011; and publications, such as the university's Annual Report and news stories produced by University Communications.
Arrangement note
The materials are arranged in five series: Series 1. Administrative Units; Series 2. Schools; Series 3. Centers and Institutes; Series 4. Events; Series 5. Publications.
Access Terms
Stanford University--Administration.; Stanford University--Public Relations.; Universities and colleges--Administration.; Universities and colleges--Public relations; Web sites.
Collection Contents
- Administrative units, 2010-2012; Series 1
  - Administrative Systems, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 6, as20121106; 4.72 megabyte(s) (154 files in 100 directories)
  - Admission and Financial Aid, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jan 6, adm2011-035; 167 megabyte(s) (1019 files in 298 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 9, admission20120109; 321 megabyte(s) (351 files in 101 directories)
    - Financial Aid, 2012-2013
      Prior to 2012, the Financial Aid website was captured as part of the Office of Admission capture.
      - 2012 Jan 9, finaid20120109; 13.7 megabyte(s) (251 files in 77 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 10, finaid20130110; 60.3 megabyte(s) (243 files in 75 directories)
  - Advisory Panel on Investment Responsibility & Licensing, 2012
    - 2012 Jul 24, apir20120724; 0.47 megabyte(s) (984 files in 14 directories)
  - Athletics, 2010-2011
    - Department of Physical Education, Recreation, and Wellness, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 19, pe201107; 3235.84 megabyte(s) (2565 files in 295 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 5, pe20121105; 3666 megabyte(s) (2945 files in 460 directories)
    - GoStanford.com, 2010-2013
      - 2010 Dec 16, athletics2011-018; 1085.44 megabyte(s) (28,871 files in 1262 directories)
      - 2012 Jan 6, gostanford20120106; 1495.04 megabyte(s) (37,816 files in 1,368 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 10, gostanford20130110; 1689.6 megabyte(s) (21,859 files in 1545 directories)
    - Home of Champions, 2011 Apr 20
      Website created to commemorate Stanford's 100th NCAA championship.
      - 2011 Apr 20, champions2011-160; 14.2 megabyte(s) (325 files in 150 directories)
  - Bechtel International Center, 2012
    - 2012 Oct 24, icenter20121024; 72.2 megabyte(s) (353 files in 55 directories)
  - Business Affairs and Chief Financial Officer, Office of the Vice President for, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 13, busaff2011-044; 2467.84 megabyte(s) (14370 files in 1270 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, vpba20120103; 48.2 megabyte(s) (237 files in 30 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, businessaffairs20130107; 4.54 megabyte(s) (118 files in 28 directories)
    - Information Security Office, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, security20120724; 0.04 megabyte(s) (17 files in 6 directories)
    - Financial Management Services, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan 18, fingate20120118; 140 megabyte(s)
      - 2013 Jan 11, fingate20130111; 123 megabyte(s) (1348 files in 169 directories)
      - Global Business Services, 2012-2013
        - 2012 Feb 13, globalops20120213; 3.75 megabyte(s) (128 files in 22 directories)
        - 2013 Feb 1, globalops20130201; 2.72 megabyte(s) (99 files in 26 directories)
  - Continuing Studies, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 15, contstud2011-011; 18.5 megabyte(s) (355 files in 24 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 9, continuing20120109; 45.4 megabyte(s) (378 files in 21 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, continuingstudies20130108; 41 megabyte(s) (415 files in 22 directories)
  - Development, Office of, 2012
    - Office of Foundation Relations, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 25, foundation20120725; 0.68 megabyte(s) (36 files in 16 directories)
  - Diversity and Access, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, diver201107; 32.3 megabyte(s) (121 files in 17 directories)
    - 2012 Oc 29, diversity20121029; 33.6 megabyte(s) (121 files in 26 directories)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, ehs201107; 3.27 megabyte(s) (84 files in 32 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 26, ehs20121026; 260 megabyte(s) (1317 files in 946 directories)
  - Export Control, 2011-2012
    As of April 2013, this site is part of the main Dean of Research site at https://doresearch.stanford.edu.
    - 2011 Jul 19, export201107; 33.9 megabyte(s) (112 files in 15 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 5, export20121105; 34.1 megabyte(s) (108 files in 15 directories)
  - Faculty Development and Diversity Office, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 15, facdev2011-014; 31.1 megabyte(s) (540 files in 140 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, facdev20120106; 47.3 megabyte(s) (313 files in 40 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, facultydevelopment20130108; 47.7 megabyte(s) (244 files in 26 directories)
  - Faculty Staff Housing, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 15, fachousing2011-010; 17.1 megabyte(s) (145 files in 22 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, fsh20120106; 25.1 megabyte(s) (165 Files in 25 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, fsh20130108; 25.8 megabyte(s) (137 files in 22 directories)
  - Faculty Senate, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, fac201107; 778 megabyte(s) (2298 files in 208 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 29, facultysenate20121029; 468 megabyte(s) (2436 files in 216 directories)
  - General Counsel, Office of, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 14, legal2011-009; 16.2 megabyte(s) (224 files in 22 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, legal20120103; 38 megabyte(s) (245 files in 24 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, ogc20130107; 44.6 megabyte(s) (191 files in 39 directories)
  - Graduate Education, Office of the Vice Provost for, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 14, graded2011-024; 11.6 megabyte(s) (315 files in 22 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, graded20120106; 30.4 megabyte(s) (379 files in 21 folders)
    - 2013 Jan 8, vpge20130108; 95.1 megabyte(s) (441 files in 33 directories)
    - Graduate Academic Policies, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 19, gap201107; 2.38 megabyte(s) (95 files in 12 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 6, gap20121106; 3.04 megabyte(s) (92 files in 12 directories)
    - Graduate Summer Institute, 2012
      - 2012 Oct 31, sgsi20121031; 1.3 megabyte(s) (96 files in 11 directories)
  - Help Center, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 15, help201107; 1.37 megabyte(s) (74 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Oct 30, helpcenter20121030; 7.76 megabyte(s) (161 files in 30 directories)
  - Human Resources, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 6, hr2011-034; 199 megabyte(s) (7940 files in 308 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, hrweb20120103; 23 megabyte(s) (774 files in 98 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, hrweb20130107; 23.5 megabyte(s) (291 files in 54 directories)
    - Benefits, 2012-2013
      Prior to 2012, this content was captured as part of the Human Resources web site.
      - 2012 Jan 3, benefits20120103; 82.1 megabyte(s) (401 files in 95 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 7, benefits20130107; 72.8 megabyte(s) (367 files in 86 directories)
    - Educational Assistance Program, 2012
      - 2012 Jan 3, hreap20120103; 4.75 megabyte(s) (52 files in 11 directories)
    - Learning and Organizational Effectiveness, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan 3, loe20120103; 51.3 megabyte(s) (124 files in 23 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 7, loe20130107; 44.7 megabyte(s) (84 files in 21 directories)
    - Operations and Systems, 2012-2013
      Prior to 2012, this content was captured as part of the Human Resources web site. Prior to 2013, it was known as the Management Information Service.
      - 2012 Jan 6, hrdata20120106; 63.6 megabyte(s) (1,519 files in 126 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 7, hrdata20130107; 108 megabyte(s) (405 files in 36 directories)
    - New Hires, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 18, new201107; 23 megabyte(s) (152 files in 29 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 1, newhire20121101; 29.6 megabyte(s) (147 files in 35 directories)
    - Staff Employment Program, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan 6, staffing20120106; 5.61 megabyte(s) (135 files in 20 folders)
      - 2013 Jan 7, staffing20120107; 21.9 megabyte(s) (132 files in 20 directories)
    - Worklife Office, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 6, worklife20121106; 41 megabyte(s) (290 files in 70 directories)
  - Institutional Research and Decision Support, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, irds201107; 26 megabyte(s) (480 files in 186 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 1, irdss20121101; 31.6 megabyte(s) (164 files in 25 directories)
  - Internal Audit and Institutional Compliance, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 2, audit20121102; 6.96 megabyte(s) (101 files in 22 directories)
  - IT Services, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 6, itservices20121106; 776 megabyte(s) (3766 files in 869 directories)
  - Land, Buildings, and Real Estate, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jan 7, lbre2011-039; 2191.36 megabyte(s) (3199 files in 338 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3-6, lbre20120103; 4352 megabyte(s) (2863 files in 286 directories)
    - Buildings and Grounds Maintenance, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 15, bgm201107; 9.4 megabyte(s) (496 files in 37 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 26, bgm20121026; 10.6 megabyte(s) (483 files in 56 directories)
    - Parking and Transportation Services, 2012
      - 2012 Aug 28, transportation20120828; 276 megabyte(s) (1125 files in 166 directories)
    - Searsville Dam, 2013 Jan 24; searsville20130124; 40.7 megabyte(s) (31 files in 27 directories)
  - Ombuds, Office of the, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, ombud201107; 0.75 megabyte(s) (39 files in 9 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 1, ombuds20121101; 0.72 megabyte(s) (34 files in 9 directories)
  - President, Office of the, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 14, president2011-007; 0.4 megabyte(s) (71 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, president20120103; 0.72 megabyte(s) (88 files in 21 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, president20120107; 0.9 megabyte(s) (88 files in 23 directories)
  - Provost, Office of the, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 14, provost2011-008; 1.34 megabyte(s) (71 files in 13 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, provost20120103; 19.5 megabyte(s) (127 files in 27 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, provost20130107; 19.6 megabyte(s) (108 files in 32 directories)
  - Postdoctoral Affairs, Office of, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, pdoc201107; 158 megabyte(s) (5532 files in 128 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 2, postdocs20121102; 144 megabyte(s) (446 files in 100 directories)
  - Public Affairs, Office of, 2011-2013
    - 2011 Jan 6, pub_aff2011-037; 22 megabyte(s) (350 files in 83 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 3, pubaff20120103; 0.96 megabyte(s) (82 files in 18 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 7, publicaffairs20130107; 0.94 megabyte(s) (78 files in 20 directories)
    - Breakfast Briefings, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, breakfast20120724; 7.5 megabyte(s) (350 files in 32 directories)
    - Government and Community Relations, 2012-2013
      Prior to 2012, the Government and Community Relations web site was captured as part of the Office of Public Affairs web site.
      - 2012 Jan 3, govcr20120103; 47.4 megabyte(s) (121 files in 31 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 7, govcr20130107; 12.1 megabyte(s) (100 files in 31 directories)
    - Special Events and Protocol, Office of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 15, osep201107; 45.7 megabyte(s) (195 files in 35 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 30, osep20121030; 46.7 megabyte(s) (160 files in 35 directories)
    - University Communications, 2011
      - 2011 Jul 15, ucomm201107; 3.79 megabyte(s) (161 files in 22 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 6, ucomm20121106; 984 megabyte(s) (6569 files in 2742 directories)
  - Public Safety, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, psafe201107; 101 megabyte(s) (277 files in 23 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 1, sudps20121101; 36.2 megabyte(s) (335 files in 24 directories)
  - Religious Life, Office for, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 15, religious2011-015; 49.2 megabyte(s) (1072 files in 174 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, 237 megabyte(s) (1,160 Files in 197 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, religiouslife20130108; 229 megabyte(s) (1211 files in 204 directories)
  - Research, Office of the Vice Provost and Dean of, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 14, research2011-012; 1.36 megabyte(s) (115 files in 17 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, dor20120106; 184 megabyte(s) (2,376 files in 201 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, dor20130108; 212 megabyte(s) (2288 files in 211 directories)
    - 2013 Apr 2, doresearch20130402; 354 megabyte(s) (5430 files in 364 directories)
    - Research Administration, Office of, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 2, ora20121102; 2160.6 megabyte(s) (2740 files in 205 directories)
    - Research Compliance, Office of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 20, 0.16 megabyte(s) (29 files in 9 directories)
      - 2012 Nov 6, researchcompliance20121106; 5.71 megabyte(s) (155 files in 83 directories)
      - Administrative Panel on Laboratory Animal Care, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Jul 18, lab201107; 13.9 megabyte(s) (95 files in 13 directories)
        - 2012 Nov 2, labanimals20121102; 0.4 megabyte(s) (27 files in 9 directories)
      - Human Subjects Research Guide, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Jul 18, humsub201107; 103 megabyte(s) (330 files in 35 directories)
        - 2012 Nov 2, humansubjects20121102; 115 megabyte(s) (333 files in 67 directories)
      - Stem Cell Research Oversight, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 6, scro20121106; 0.61 megabyte(s) (38 files in 18 directories)
    - Research Policy Handbook, 2011
      As of April 2013, this site is part of the Dean of Research main website at https://doresearch.stanford.edu.
      - 2011 Sep 14, rph201109; 7.89 megabyte(s) (167 files in 13 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 9, rph20120409; 8.09 megabyte(s) (168 files in 13 directories)
  - Residential and Dining Enterprises, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 19, rde201107; 328 megabyte(s) (2210 files in 242 directories)
    - 2012 Dec 7, rde20121207; 283 megabyte(s) (3132 files in 562 directories)
  - Risk Management Department, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 1, risk20121101; 6.1 megabyte(s) (73 files in 10 directories)
  - Science Outreach Office, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, oso201107; 23 megabyte(s) (516 files in 69 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 1, oso20121101; 14.6 megabyte(s) (532 files in 102 directories)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy Office, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, harass201107; 4.83 megabyte(s) (59 files in 9 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 1, harass20121101; 3.23 megabyte(s) (52 files in 9 directories)
  - Sustainability, Office of, 2012
    - 2012 Nov 7, ssu20121107; 3.79 megabyte(s) (85 files in 15 directories)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 2010
    - 2010 Dec 16, alum2011-017; 356 megabyte(s) (5855 files in 728 directories)
  - Stanford Management Company, 2010-2012
    - 2010 Dec 15, smc2011-016; 3.23 megabyte(s) (105 files in 36 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, smc20120106; 34.6 megabyte(s) (117 files in 37 directories)
  - Stanford University Libraries, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 17, sulair2011-028; 4188.16 megabyte(s) (46,821 files in 2459 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 9, sulair20120109; 8785.92 megabyte(s) (52,969 files in 3,496 directories)
    - Copyright and Fair Use website, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 15, fair201107; 19.2 megabyte(s) (596 files in 136 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 26, fairuse20121026; 18.8 megabyte(s) (433 files in 143 directories)
    - Academic Computing Services, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, acomp20120724; 105 megabyte(s) (1493 files in 140 directories)
    - SUL News, 2013
      - 2013 Mar 20, SUL_News20130320; 9.4 megabyte(s) (627 files in 248 directories)
  - Student Affairs, Office of the Vice Provost for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jan 14, stu_aff2011-049; 864 megabyte(s) (10,121 files in 1530 directories)
      This capture also includes the websites of the Career Development Center, El Centro Chicano, Asian American Activities Center, Bechtel International Center, Black Community Services Center, Office of Graduate Admissions, the Graduate Life Office, Judicial Affairs, University Registrar, Student Activities and Leadership, Tresidder Meeting Services, Vaden Health Center, Women's Community Center, and Haas Center for Public Service.
    - 2012 Jan 18, studentaff20120118; 1187.84 megabyte(s) (11419 files in 1705 directories)
    - Alcohol @ Stanford, 2012
      - 2012 Jul 24, aab20120724; 2.54 megabyte(s) (146 files in 14 directories)
    - Asian American Activities Center, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 5, a3c20121105; 74.1 megabyte(s) (440 files in 525 directories)
    - Bing Overseas Studies Program, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 1, bosp20121101; 461 megabyte(s) (2147 files in 131 directories)
    - Judicial Affairs, 2012
      - 2012 Jan 20, judicial20120120; 723 megabyte(s) (416 files in 143 directories)
    - Veden Health Center, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 6, vaden20121106; 17.8 megabyte(s) (373 files in 40 directories)
  - Technology Licensing, Office of, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, otl201107; 327 megabyte(s) (300 files in 109 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 2, otl20121102; 66.9 megabyte(s) (290 files in 18 directories)
  - Treasurer, Office of the, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, trea201107; 2.3 megabyte(s) (308 files in 61 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 2, treasurer20121102; 2.1 megabyte(s) (269 files in 61 directories)
    - Bondholder Information website, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Jul 15, bond201107; 394 megabyte(s) (131 files in 19 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 25, bondholder20121025; 66.8 megabyte(s) (136 files in 19 directories)
  - Undergraduate Education, Office of the Vice Provost for, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jan 10, ue2011-042; 524 megabyte(s) (7589 files in 454 directories)
      This capture also includes the websites of the Center for Teaching and Learning, Introductory Seminars, Introduction to the Humanities, Program in Writing and Rhetoric, Hume Writing Center, and Structured Liberal Education.
    - 2012 Jan 17, undergrad20120117; 713 megabyte(s) (17,181 files in 491 directories)
    - Freshman Sophomore College, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Jul 19, frosoco201107; 78.9 megabyte(s) (6478 files in 79 directories)
      - 2012 Jan 18, frosoco20120118; 3.61 megabyte(s) (60 files in 12 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 11, frosoco20130111; 8.23 megabyte(s) (72 files in 20 directories)
    - Structured Liberal Education, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan, sle20120118; 2.7 megabyte(s) (221 files in 83 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 22, sle20130122; 102 megabyte(s) (315 files in 89 directories)
    - Introductory Seminars, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan 18, introsem20120118; 30.3 megabyte(s) (98 files in 11 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 11, introsems20130111; 36.2 megabyte(s) (82 files in 9 directories)
    - Undergraduate Academic Life, 2012
      - 2012 Jan 18, ual20120118; 347 megabyte(s) (804 files in 80 directories)
    - Program in Writing and Rhetoric, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Jan 18, pwr20120118; 49.4 megabyte(s) (483 files in 57 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 22, pwr20130122; 80.5 megabyte(s) (638 files in 128 directories)
  - University Budget Office, 2010-2013
    - 2010 Dec 15, budget2011-013; 36.3 megabyte(s) (540 files in 140 directories)
    - 2012 Jan 6, budget20120106; 64.9 megabyte(s) (445 files in 28 directories)
    - 2013 Jan 8, budget20130108; 46.7 megabyte(s) (481 files in 42 directories)
  - University Corporate Relations, Office of, 2011-2012
    - 2011 Jul 18, corp201107; 0.37 megabyte(s) (28 files in 9 directories)
    - 2012 Nov 2, corporate20121102; 0.36 megabyte(s) (26 files in 9 directories)
- Schools, 2010-2011; Series 2
  - Business, Graduate School of, 2011-2012
    - Graduate School of Business, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Jan 7, csi_2011-135; 1863.68 megabyte(s) (18269 files in 1573 directories)
      - 2012 Jan 26, gsb20120126; 1884.16 megabyte(s) (17048 files in 1617 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 17, gsb20130117; 2376 megabyte(s) (12,383 files in 1336 directories)
    - Center for Social Innovation, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 18, gsb2011-038; 598 megabyte(s) (10,604 files in 411 directories)
      - 2012 March 13, csi20120313; 547 megabyte(s) (9344 files in 502 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 8, csi20130307; 1187 megabyte(s) (11,621 files in 563 directories)
    - Corporate Governance Research Project, 2012
      - 2012 Oct 25, crgp20121025; 7.54 megabyte(s) (204 files in 104 directories)
  - Earth Sciences, 2011-2013
    - School of Earth Sciences, 2011
      - 2011 Jan 18, 9779.2 megabyte(s) (49,534 files in 1336 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 12, earthsci20130312; 18432 megabyte(s) (56,540 files in 2,958 directories)
    - Center for Resevoir Forecasting, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 20, scrf201109; 149 megabyte(s) (199 files in 7 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 17, scrf20120905; 2621 megabyte(s) (263 files in 12 directories)
    - Clean Energy Conversion Lab, 2012
      - 2012 Sep 4, cec20120904; 197 megabyte(s) (167 files in 6 directories)
    - Climate and Earth Systems Dynamics Group, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 20, omra201109; 238 megabyte(s) (137 files in 4 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 6, omramom20120906; 134 megabyte(s) (136 files in 4 directories)
    - Climate,Tectonics and Landscape Evolution, Research Group on, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 3, crg201110; 69.8 megabyte(s) (106 files in 8 directories)
    - Dunbar Group, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, dunbar201110; 1.76 megabyte(s) (18 files in 4 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 7, dunbar20120907; 2.1 megabyte(s) (22 files in 4 directories)
    - Earth Systems Program, 2011
      - 2011 May 18, esys_2011-133; 4.25 megabyte(s) (60 files in 25 directories)
    - Emmett Interdisciplinary Program in Environment and Resources, 2011
      - 2011 May 18, eiper_2011-134; 598 megabyte(s) (10,604 files in 411 directories)
    - Environmental Earth System Science
      - 2011 May 17, eess_2011-131; 4.25 megabyte(s) (60 files in 25 directories)
    - Geological and Environmental Sciences, Department of, 2011
      - 2011 May 17, ges_2011-132; 487 megabyte(s) (438 files in 16 directories)
    - Ocean Biogeochemistry Lab, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 3, ocean201110; 325 megabyte(s) (7276 files in 117 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 6, ocean20120906; 1382.4 megabyte(s) (7,297 files in 135 directories)
    - Project on Deep-water Depositional Systems, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 17, spodds201110; 100 megabyte(s) (210 files in 18 directories)
      - 2012 Oct 24, spodds20121024; 304 megabyte(s) (198 files in 18 directories)
    - Soil and Environmental Biogeochemistry, 2011-2012; soils20120907; 1044.5 megabyte(s) (2,777 files in 150 directories)